[{"id":1,"question":"Which types of indexes are available in CosmosDB?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"range and spatial","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"secondary and primary key","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"secondary and spatial","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"range and primary key","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":2,"question":"You want to connect a DynamoDB stream to AWS Lambda function?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"DynamoDB table","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB trigger","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB item","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB index","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":3,"question":"To index a field that holds an array value in MongoDB, which index type do you create?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"partial","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"sparse","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"compound","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"multikey","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":4,"question":"You want to test HBASE on your laptop using the fewest number of steps. What do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Set up Hadoop in pseudo-distributed mode.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Set up HBASE in local mode.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Set up HBASE in pseudo-distributed mode.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Set up Hadoop in local mode.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":5,"question":"You need to create a document database that supports database triggers. Which NoSQL database should you use?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"DynamoDB","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"BigTable","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Redis","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"MongoDB","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":6,"question":"What is recommended size for Redis keys?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"medium","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"short","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"single bit","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"long","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":7,"question":"You need to design security for DynamoDB to allow users read-only access to certain items and attributes in a table. What do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Use lAM policy conditions","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use lAM roles","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use VPC endpoint","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use lAM policies","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":8,"question":"What does redis use to sort the elements of a sorted set?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Scores.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Ids.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Values.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Keys.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":9,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Dump the collection data, drop the collection, create a new collection and shard key, import the data.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Add second shard key and drop the first shard key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Dump the collection data, drop the collection, presplit the data, create a new collection and shard key, import the data.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Drop and recreate the shard key.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":10,"question":"Polyglot storage means using multiple types of what in the same application?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Security systems.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Database systems.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Storage systems.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Query systems.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":11,"question":"You need to implement the simplest possible scalable, in-memory cache for your AWS application. Which service do you select?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Elasticache using Memcached.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB Accelerator (DAX).","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Elasticache using Redis.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":12,"question":"You are doing data modelling for Google BigTable. Which statement expresses if and when you should split entities across multiple rows?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Keep all information for an entity in a single row. Store related entities in adjacent rows.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Keep all information for an entity in a single row.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Split entities across multiple rows if the entity data is over thousands of MBs, or if it does not need atomic updates and reads.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Split entities across multiple rows if the entity data is over hundreds of MBs, or if it does not need atomic updates and reads.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":13,"question":"Which two characteristics define Amazon Quantum Ledger Database?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Key-value data model; transactionally consistent with ACID semantics.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Document data model; transactionally consistent with ACID semantics.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Key-value data model; transactions with tunable consistency.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Document data model; transactions with tunable consistency.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":14,"question":"You need to design the primary key for DynamoDB based on three attributes. What do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Designate all three fields as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Concatenate all three fields into one new field, then designate that new field as the primary key.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Designate two fields of the three fields as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Concatenate two fields into one new field, then designate that new field and the remaining field as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":15,"question":"You need to design the primary key for DynamoDB based on three attributes. What do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Designate all three fields as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Concatenate all three fields into one new field, then designate that new field as the primary key.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Designate two fields of the three fields as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Concatenate two fields into one new field, then designate that new field and the remaining field as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":16,"question":"Which of these data types should you avoid in designing a Google Bigtable row key?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"multi-valued identifiers","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"string identifiers","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"timesstamps","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"frequently updated identifiers","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":17,"question":"Your startup is building a prototype that has an evolving schema. Your data will be eventually consistent. Your application is hosted in AWS. Which databse do you choose?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Neptune","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DocumentDB","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Amazon Aurora","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":18,"question":"You need to create a scalable databse that allows you to share documents across authorized mobile clients in real time. What Google NoSQL database should you use?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Memorystore","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Datastore","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Firebase","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Bigtable","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":19,"question":"You want to test HBase on your laptop using the fewest number of steps. What do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Set up HBase in local mode.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Set up Hadoop in pseudo-distributed mode.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Set up HBase in pseudo-distributed mode.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Set up Hadoop in local mode.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":20,"question":"You need to design security for DynamoDB to allow users read-obly access to certain items and attriutes in a table. What do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Use IAM roles.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use IAM plicy conditions.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Use a VPC endpoint.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use IAM plicies.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":21,"question":"You need to design a primary key for DynamoDb based on three attributes. What do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Concatenate all three fields into into one new field, than disignate that new field as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Concatenate two fileds into one new field, than disignate that new field and the remaining field as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Designate all three fields as the primary key.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Designate two filds of the three fields as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":22,"question":"What does Redis use to sort the elements of a sorted set?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"keys","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"values","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"scroes","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"ids","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":23,"question":"You need to create a document database that supports database triggers. Which NoSQL database should you use?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"DynamoDb","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Redis","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"MongoDB","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Bigtable","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":24,"question":"Which statement is preferred Cypher code for Neo4j?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"MATCH (:Person)-->(:Card)-->(:Company) RETURN count(vehicle)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Match (:Person)-->(:Car):(vehicle:Car)-->(:Company) RETURN count(vehicle)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"MATCH (:Person)-->(vehicle:Car)-->(:Company) RETURN count(vehicle)","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"MATCH (:Person)-->(:Card), (vehicle:Car)-->(:Company) RETURN count(vehicle)","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":25,"question":"You need multi-item ACID transactions with snapshot isolation within a partition for your cloud-based application. Which NoSQL databse do you choose?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Bigtable","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"GraphDB","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cosmos DB","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":26,"question":"You need to control your application's batch updates destination for your Bigtable multinode cluster. Which action do you take?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Create a custom app profile to route batch updates.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create a custom app profile to route the batch update from that client.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Update the default app profile to route the natch update from that client.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Use the default app profile to route batch updates.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":27,"question":"Polyglot storage mean using multiple types of what in the same application?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"security systems","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"databse systems","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"query systems","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"storage systems","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":28,"question":"Your query to verify that your Redis key is configured to support expiring user information on a defined interval returns -2, What does this value indicate?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The queried key value expired in the last two secodns.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The queried key value exists, but has no associated expire value.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The queried key value does not exist.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"There are two expired keys with this value.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":29,"question":"You are designing a MongoDB schema to support queries that will include lookups. What should you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Create an index on the key value used as the primary key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create an index on the key value used as the foreign key.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create a multicolumn index on the key value used as the foreign key and the most unique column in the document.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Create a multicolumn index on the key value used as the primary and also the forign key.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":30,"question":"What is the aggregation operator for a join concept in MongoDB?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"$group","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"$match","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"$lookup","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"$project","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":31,"question":"For your mobile application, you need to select a Google cloud databse that can support compound, filtered document queries. Which do you choose?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Cloud SQL","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cloud Spanner","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cloud Firestore","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Cloud Firebase","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":32,"question":"To bulk load data into Amazon Neputn, what do you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Upload data to S3 VPC endpoint, Use the Neptun loader to load from s3 into your Neptune instance","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Ad data to a Kinesis stream, and use the Neptune loade to load from S# into your Neptun instance.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Add data to a Kisnesis stream, and create a Kinesis stream VPC endpoint. Use the Nepune loader to load from S3into your Neptune instance.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Upload data to S Use the neptune loader to load from S3 into your Neptune instance.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":33,"question":"You need to create a pub/sub server. Which databse do you use?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Neo4j","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cassandra","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Redis","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"MyS","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":34,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[]},{"id":35,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"DynamoDb table","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB trigger","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"DynamoDB item","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DYnamoDB index","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":36,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"secondery and primary key","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"secondary and spatial","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"range and spatial","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"range and primary key","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":37,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"horizontally, infinitely","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"vertically, horizontally","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"vertically, infinitely","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"horizonally, vertically","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":38,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"a relational databse","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a columnstore databse","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a document databse","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a graph database","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":39,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Rows become labes: bales become nodes.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Tables become labels: rows become nodes.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Tables become collections: rows become items.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Rows become collections: tables become items.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":40,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"sparse","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"compound","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"partial","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"multikey","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":41,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Delete the .monorc.js file and restart mongo shell.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the mongo shell to create a command with --norc option","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Rem all lines in the .mongorc.js file ad restart mongo shell.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the mongo shell to create a command with --nodedefault option.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":42,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"long","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"short","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"medium","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a single bit","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":43,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"map","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"set","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"list","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"stack","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":44,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"aws dynamodb query --table-name MusicCollection --key file://key.json","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"aws dynamodb get-item --table-name MusicCollection --key file://key.json","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"aws dynamodb select --table-name MusicCollection --key file://key.json","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"aws dynamodb put-item --table-name MusicCollection --key file://key.json","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":45,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"the amount of service calls","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the number of minutes","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the amount of service costs","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the number of nines","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":46,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"You assign a default AWS encryption key to your table to encrypt data.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"You create an AWS encryption key and assign it to your table to encrypt data.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"None. Data is encrypted by default.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"You create an AWS encryption key and assign it to your database to encrypt data.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":47,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Implement a SortedSet object to generate a value.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the GUID keyword to generate a value.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Implement a List object to generate a value.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the INCR keyword to generate a value","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":48,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"smembers","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"returnall","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"sunion","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"sismember","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":49,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"detailQueryExecution()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"showPlan()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"explain()","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"describe()","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":50,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The global secondary indexes in DynamoDB are consistent, and are not guaranteed to return correct results.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The global secondary indexes in DynamoDB are transactionally consistent, and are guaranteed to return correct results.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The global secondary indexes in DynamoDB are partially consistent, and are not guaranteed to return correct results.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The global secondary indexes in DynamoDB are eventually consistent, and are not guaranteed to return correct results.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":51,"code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"ADD mystream * sensor-id 1234 temperature 19.8 1518951480106-1","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"UPDATE mystream * sensor-id 1234 temperature 19.8 1518951480106-3","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"XADD mystream * sensor-id 1234 temperature 9.8 1518951480106-0","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"INSERT mystream * sensor-d 1234 temperature 19.8 15181480106-2","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":52,"code":"var indexCollection = function(db) {return co(function*() {...});};","reference":"```","choices":[{"text":"`const results = yield db.table('restaurants').createIndex({\"name\": 1}, null); return results;`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`const results = yield db.collection('restaurants').createIndex({\"name\": 0}, null); return results;`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`const results = yield db.collection('restaurants').createIndex({\"name\": 1}, null); return results;`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`const results = yield db.table('restaurants').createIndex({\"name\": 0}, null); return results;`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":53,"code":"MATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c, MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p, MATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type;   MATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c, MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p, MATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type   MATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c AND MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p, AND MATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type;   MATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c;MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p; MATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type;  ### Q53. You need to create a scalable database that supports immutable writes. What do you use?","choices":[{"text":"\nMATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c, MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p,\nMATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type;\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"\nMATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c, MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p,\nMATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"\nMATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c AND MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p,\nAND MATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type;\n","code":true,"answer":false},{"text":"\nMATCH (c:Company {name: 'Neo4j'}) RETURN c;MATCH (p:Person) WHERE p.name = 'Jennifer' RETURN p;\nMATCH (t:Technology)-[:LIKES]-(a:Person {name: 'Jennifer'}) RETURN t.type;\n","code":true,"answer":false}]},{"id":54,"question":"You need to create a data store for the catalog for your new ecommerce application. Your company is a startup, so the catalog schema may evolve. Which do you choose?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Neo4j","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Redis","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"MySQL","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"MongoDB","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":55,"question":"You need to select a NoSQL database for heavy aggregate query workloads. Which type do you choose?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"graph","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"key-value","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"document","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"columnstore","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":56,"question":"You need to select a columnstore database that enforce built-in data types. You want to add indexes to improve performance for known workloads. Which do you choose?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Cassandra","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Bigtable","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Redis","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"HBase","answer":false,"code":false}]}]